One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Tsuru Returns the Favor
Tsuru İyiliği Geri Ödüyor
It's time you cut your visit short.
Tatilinizi kısa kesseniz iyi olur.
Don't you know who pulls the strings in this country?
Bu ülkeyi perdeler arkasından kimin yönettiğini biliyor musunuz?
No idea!
Ne bileyim!
It's Kaido, right?!
Kaido, değil mi?
We're here to...
Yonko'nun...
take down an Emperor!
canına okumaya geldik zaten!
Hey, Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Kin'emon said we shouldn't say things like that, either!
Kin'emon böyle şeyler de söylemememiz gerektiğine dikkat çekmişti.
Wha...?
Ne...?
That was a lie!
Götümden uydurdum!
I don't know who!
Ben de bilmiyorum!
The probability of you two surviving the month...
Önümüzdeki aya çıkabilme ihtimaliniz...
is 19 percent.
yüzde 19.
By the way, where'd you get that sword?
Bu arada, elindeki kılıcı nereden buldun?
Some named blade, thus and verily.
Bir isimli kılıç-de gozaru, değil mi?
Yeah, I'm certain it's a named blade.
Evet, harbiden de isimli kılıç aurası taşıyor.
Let me see it for a sec.
Ver de bir bakayım.
No way!
Vermem!
You can't use a sword anyway so just give it to me!
Nasılsa kullanmayı bilmiyorsun, ver gitsin işte!
I'll cut them up, verily!
Hepsini biçeceğim-de-gozaru!
Charge.
Hücum.
This is a sword fight, verily!
Kılıç dövüşü-de-gozaru!
Don't throw the scabbard!
Kını fırlatmasana lan!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Pistol!
Tabanca!
It's not a damn pistol!
Tabanca ne alaka be!
Even the lizard's after me!
Kertenkele bile saldırıyor!
Damn you!
Ağzına sıçtığımın...
Straw Sword.
Hasır Kılıç.
What kind of sword is that?!
Ne biçim bir kılıç o?
That poor lizard!
Kertenkeleye acıdım.
That was fast!
Çok çabuk oldu!
Impressive.
Şanına yaraşır.
What just happened?!
Ne oldu öyle?
Minus One Life.
Bir Can Eksildi.
These strawmen represent my subordinates.
Hasır bebekler, adamlarımı temsil ediyor.
I can store them in my body with my Straw-Straw power...
Hasır-Hasır Meyvesi gücüyle adamlarımı bedenimde tutarak...
so I won't be harmed.
zarar görmüyorum.
If I store ten of them, I can die ten times.
Bedenimde on kişi tutuyorsam on kez ölebilirim.
Now, let's play a game.
Pekâlâ, oyun başlasın.
A game?!
Oyun mu?
That's right...
Evet...
With this Strawman's Card!
Hasır Adam Kartı'yla başlıyorum!
I'm not so honorable that I'd face two of the Worst Generation on equal footing.
En Kötü Nesil'den iki korsanla adil biçimde çarpışacak kadar onurlu biri değilim.
He's a bigger pain in the ass than I thought...
Sandığımdan da baş belası çıktı.
but I should've figured!
Ne bekliyordum ki?
Let's begin.
Başlıyorum.
The Reversed Fool!
Ters Aptal!
Damn, this signifies internal discord.
Eyvah, yoldaşlar arası çatışma.
Sorry, I'll draw a better card next time.
Kusura bakmayın, bir dahakine daha iyi bir kart çekeceğim.
I must accept the risks because some cards can push me beyond my limits.
Riski kabullenmek zorundayım, zira bazı kartlar sınırlarımı aşmamı sağlıyor.
Hey! What are you doing, boy?!
Hey! N'apıyorsun be köpek?!
Hawkins!
Hawkins-san!
Fear not.
Telaşlanmayın.
Tama! Stay with us, Tama!
Tama! Dayan Tama!
She's burning up!
Yanıyor resmen!
That's must be why the dog's in a hurry.
Köpek bu yüzden koşmaya başladı.
You bastards!
Şerefsizler!
We won't let you escape!
Bir yere kaçamazsınız!
Hawkins! They're getting away!
Hawkins-san! Kaçıyorlar!
I drew a good card.
İyi bir kart çektim.
The Reversed Hierophant.
Ters Aziz.
The card of pursuit!
Takip kartı!
Hey, Luffy!
Hey, Luffy!
Protect the kid!
Veledi koru!
I'll...
Onu...
handle...
ben...
this!
hallederim!
You're actually pretty tough.
Çetin ceviz çıktın.
Nails?!
Çivi mi?!
Two-Sword Style...
İki Kılıç Stili...
Nigiri...
Çift Biçen...
Toro...
Kule Tırmanışı...
Samon!
Kum Çekilişi!
Should we go after them, Hawkins?!
Peşlerine düşelim mi, Hawkins-san?
The Hierophant.
Aziz.
It's the card of assistance.
bir destek kartıdır.
Someone will lead them away to safety...
Yani birinin rehberliğinde sağ salim kaçacakları anlamına geliyor.
What an annoying guy...
Biraz uğraştıran bir tip.
So, how's the kid doing?
Peki velet ne durumda?
So warm!
Yanıyor!
Her temperature keeps rising.
Ateşi yükseliyor...
Dog!
Köpek!
Run faster!
Acele et!
Huh? What's the problem?
Ha? Sorun ne?
Wait... are you...?
Yoksa...
Are you lost?!
kayıp mı oldun lan?
We've got no time to waste...
Kaybedecek vaktimiz yok.
Let's just...
Neyse,
go right.
sağa gidelim bakalım.
You should go left.
Sola gitmelisiniz.
You samurai are so strong.
Oldukça güçlü samuraylarsınız.
Who are you?!
Sen de kimsin?
I can't believe you repelled Hawkins.
Hawkins'i püskürtebildiğinize inanamıyorum!
You're...
Sen...
I'm the one you saved earlier, green gentleman.
Biraz önce beni kurtarmıştınız, yeşil beyefendi.
My name is Tsuru.
Adım Tsuru.
Otsuru Teahouse Owner
Otsuru Çay Evi Sahibi
Were you... hiding in his tail all this time?!
Yoksa bunca zamandır kuyrukta mı saklanıyordun?
Yes!
Evet!
Thank you for saving me.
Hayatımı kurtardığınız için minnettarım.
Here!
Alın!
Could you at least wipe the sweat off of her?
En azından terini siler misiniz?
Oh! Thanks!
İyi dedin! Teşekkürler!
I hope this doesn't sound too presumptuous...
Küstahlık olarak görmezseniz...
but would you allow me to care for young Otama?
o çocuğu, Otama-chan'ı bana emanet eder misiniz?
You know her?
Onu tanıyor musun?
Yes.
Evet.
I see!
Demek öyle!
Please do!
Lütfen!
She drank the polluted river water because she was so hungry.
Açlığını bastırmak için zehirli nehir suyundan içmiş.
Instead of searching for a doctor...
Öyleyse doktor aramak yerine...
please bring her to my teahouse.
çay evime gelin lütfen.
Tea?!
Çay mı?
This is no time for tea!
Çay yudumlamanın sırası mı be!
If we don't hurry up, she's gonna die!
Elimizi çabuk tutmazsak nalları dikecek!
I don't know this kid, so it might not be any of my business but...
Velet kimdir, kimlerdendir bilmesem de...
No, no...
Hayır...
We have a medical herb that is effective against the river's poison.
Nehir zehrine karşı oldukça tesiri olan şifalı bir bitkimiz var.
That'll be the best way to treat Otama's condition.
Otama-chan'ın tedavisi için en doğrusu olur.
I see.
Anladım.
Then please, help us!
Öyleyse yardım edin lütfen!
Thank you!
Teşekkürler!
To return the favor I owe you...
Minnet borcumu ödemek adına...
let me treat you, too, green gentleman...
sizi de tedavi etmeme müsaade edin, yeşil beyefendi.
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore Town Kuri Wano
Okobore (Artık) Kasabası Kuri Wano
Here you go.
Buyurun.
The teahouse's dumplings are a rare treat.
Çay evinizde arada bir yiyebildiğim bu dangolar olmasa...
They're the only things...
beni hayata bağlayan...
that keep me going.
bir şey kalmazdı.
You exaggerate...
Mübalağa ediyorsunuz.
Soon, you'll be able to eat as many as you want just like you used to.
Yakında tıpkı eskiden olduğu gibi dilediğiniz kadar yiyebileceksiniz.
I hope so...
Umarım öyle olur.
Okiku Teahouse Waitress
Okiku Çay Evi Garsonu
Hey, old man, the place is closing now!
Lan moruk, dükkânın kapanış saati geldi!
Get lost!
Yaylan!
Now, Okiku.
Baksana, Okiku...
You can't pay the street tax, right?
Vergini ödeyemiyorsun, değil mi-pe?
All I'm saying is that I'll help you.
Yardım eli uzatayım diyorum sadece.
If you become my wife...
Karım olursan...
you won't have to work!
çalışmana gerek kalmaz!
Every day, you'd be able to eat as much delicious food from the farm as you want!
Tarladan her gün canının istediği kadar nefis yemekler yiyebilirsin-pe!
Our social standings are too different.
Konumlarımız birbirinden çok farklı.
If you're not ordering anything, would you please...
Siparişiniz yoksa lütfen...
take your leave?
ayrılın.
I don't wanna eat anything from this place!
Bu çöplükten tek lokma yemek istemiyorum!
The dumplings and tea are made from others' leftovers!
Artıklardan yapılma dango ve çayı n'apayım?
Say, you do know who I am, right?
Bak hele, kim olduğumu pek bilmiyorsun, değil mi-pe?
I'm a famous yokozuna from the capital.
Başkentte nam salmış bir yokozuna'yım.
I'm the best sumo wrestler in Wano,
Wano'nun en güçlü sumo güreşçisi yani!
Urashima!
Adım Urashima!
It's time you quit this seedy teahouse!
Bu fare deliğini bırak!
You need to stop living off of someone's leftovers, so that you and I...
Onun bunun artığıyla rezil bir hayat yaşamayı bırak da hani diyorum benimle...
so that we can... y'know...?
Ne diyorsun?
Okiku!
Okiku-chan!
Miss Otsuru!
Otsuru-san!
Otama drank poisoned water from the river!
Otama-chan nehrin zehrinden içmiş!
Oh! That's serious!
Olamaz! Durum ciddi!
Please! Do what you can to help her!
Lütfen! Kızı bir şekilde kurtar!
Okiku!
Okiku-chan!
Brew the cinquefoil!
Beşparmak otunu kaynat!
Of course, right away!
Tabii ki, hemen!
Hey!
Lan!
Who are you idiots?!
Siz de kimin nesisiniz-pe?!
Get out the way.
Çekil kenara.
Huh?!
Ha?!
Why would I have to do that...?!
Neden senin dediğini yapayım?
Okiku! I have a match in Bakura Town later!
Okiku! Bakura Kasabası'nda bir müsabakam olacak-pe!
If you're interested, come and see how strong I am!
Gücümü merak ediyorsan izlemeye gelirsin!
Atop a Mountain...
Bir dağın zirvesinde...
It's them, isn't it?!
Doğru gördüm, değil mi?
It's the Straw Hats!
Hasır Şapkalar!
Should I go tell them before they make any trouble?!
Arıza çıkarmalarını beklemeden gidip konuşsam mı?
You'd better not!
Hiç yeltenme!
You'll draw people's attention!
Fazla göze batarsın!
For now, let's just report this to the captain.
Şimdilik durumu kaptana iletelim.